# HA MY NG<u>UYEN</u>

#### BASIC INFORMATION

An outgoing, self-motivated individual who is thriving for new experiences with positive attitude. Growing up in Viet Nam and being shaped by European culture, I have an unquenchable thirst for knowledge in customer service and problem solving. Since I enjoy new challenges and experiences, I can work well under pressure.

#### **EDUCATION**

Lapland University of Applied Sciences 9/2016 - 6/2021 Bachelor of Tourism and Hospitality Management

Le Quy Don High School 9/2012 - 5/2015

#### **CONTACT DETAILS**

Email: my.310390@gmail.com Phone: +358 45 787 235 86

Address: Opastinsilta 2A, 40, 00520,

Helsinki, FI

## **EXPERIENCE**

## Marketing and INT Housing Intern

Opiskelijan Tampere, 05/2019 - 10/2019

- Handle housing applications and offers.
- Draft rental agreements and invoices.
- Process housing supports via e-mails, phone and service desk.
- Create social media content on Facebook and Instagram to promote local business and activities to students in Tampere.
- Represent Opiskeljan Tampere in students events.
- Design and assist the implementation of Opiskeljan Tampere's marketing campaigns.

#### Seasonal Tour Guide

Santa Park Oy, 11/2018 - 01/2019

- Create inspiration of happiness, peace and value of friendship for children and bring the most memorable Christmas atmosphere.
- Interactively serve and satisfy customers from different cultures.
- Increase sales about various Christmas presents and souvenirs specialised of Rovaniemi - the hometown of Santa Claus
- Teamwork with international colleagues.

## **Restaurant Trainee**

Hotel Tropic Park, 05/2018 - 08/2018

- Work as the buffet restaurant trainee of a 4 stars hotel in Spain.
- Interact positively with customers while promoting hotel facilities and services.
- · Manage the cashier during the shifts.
- Organise tables for customers during the busy time in the restaurant.
- Serve orders for customers in different areas.
- Keep in touch with the kitchen to make sure the restaurant has enough food to serve customers.
- Resolve customer complaints.